A heart-stopping adventure!
BloodRayne II: Deliverance is a action, horror,
western film directed by Uwe Boll.
Rayne, a half-human half-vampire warrior, is in the America's 1880's Wild West to
stop the vampired Billy the Kid and his posse of vampire cowboys.
Rayne, played by Natassia Malthe.
Billy the Kid, played by Zack Ward.
Pat Garret, played by Michael Paré.
Muller, played by Brendan Fletcher.
Newton Piles, played by Chris Coppola.
The Preacher, played by Michael Eklund.
BloodRayne 2: Deliverance (also known as BloodRayne 2 or BloodRayne: Deliverance) is a 2007
direct-to-DVD Western horror film set in 1880s America and directed by Uwe Boll.
It is a sequel to the 2005 film BloodRayne, which was also
directed by Boll, and stars Kristanna Loken.
In Deliverance, Natassia Malthe replaces Loken in the lead role.
BloodRayne 2: Deliverance was released in the US on
September 18, 2007 and in Germany on November 30.
Like its predecessor, the film received negative reviews from critics.
The tone is dark.